t+0.000s  camera stamp 1790762807.614176
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=0 steer=0  lidar_obstacle_in_sweep
t+0.067s  camera stamp 1790762807.680913
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+0.133s  camera stamp 1790762807.747419
t+0.200s  camera stamp 1790762807.814281
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+0.267s  camera stamp 1790762807.881326
t+0.334s  camera stamp 1790762807.948555
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+0.466s  camera stamp 1790762808.080574
t+0.533s  camera stamp 1790762808.147586
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+0.599s  camera stamp 1790762808.213599
t+0.667s  camera stamp 1790762808.281356
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+0.736s  camera stamp 1790762808.350355
t+0.866s  camera stamp 1790762808.480309
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+0.933s  camera stamp 1790762808.546949
t+1.004s  camera stamp 1790762808.618385
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+1.139s  camera stamp 1790762808.753272
t+1.201s  camera stamp 1790762808.814957
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+1.268s  camera stamp 1790762808.881711
t+1.334s  camera stamp 1790762808.948579
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+1.474s  camera stamp 1790762809.087793
t+1.534s  camera stamp 1790762809.147696
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+1.601s  camera stamp 1790762809.214937
t+1.668s  camera stamp 1790762809.282359
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+1.802s  camera stamp 1790762809.416036
t+1.870s  camera stamp 1790762809.484180
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+1.934s  camera stamp 1790762809.547840
t+2.003s  camera stamp 1790762809.617383
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+2.134s  camera stamp 1790762809.748111
t+2.200s  camera stamp 1790762809.814094
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+2.271s  camera stamp 1790762809.885603
t+2.341s  camera stamp 1790762809.954763
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+2.400s  camera stamp 1790762810.013812
t+2.533s  camera stamp 1790762810.147508
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+2.601s  camera stamp 1790762810.214775
t+2.671s  camera stamp 1790762810.285612
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+2.800s  camera stamp 1790762810.414058
t+2.866s  camera stamp 1790762810.480385
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+2.934s  camera stamp 1790762810.548486
t+3.005s  camera stamp 1790762810.618746
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+3.137s  camera stamp 1790762810.751555
t+3.200s  camera stamp 1790762810.814239
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+3.267s  camera stamp 1790762810.881201
t+3.333s  camera stamp 1790762810.947574
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+3.467s  camera stamp 1790762811.081276
t+3.535s  camera stamp 1790762811.149201
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+3.601s  camera stamp 1790762811.214686
t+3.672s  camera stamp 1790762811.286348
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+3.801s  camera stamp 1790762811.415670
t+3.867s  camera stamp 1790762811.481052
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+3.933s  camera stamp 1790762811.547017
t+4.000s  camera stamp 1790762811.613843
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+4.135s  camera stamp 1790762811.748833
t+4.204s  camera stamp 1790762811.817999
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+4.284s  camera stamp 1790762811.897977
t+4.334s  camera stamp 1790762811.947770
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+4.470s  camera stamp 1790762812.083810
t+4.533s  camera stamp 1790762812.147308
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+4.601s  camera stamp 1790762812.215189
t+4.674s  camera stamp 1790762812.287838
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+4.805s  camera stamp 1790762812.419660
t+4.866s  camera stamp 1790762812.480420
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+4.936s  camera stamp 1790762812.549751
t+5.001s  camera stamp 1790762812.614775
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+5.136s  camera stamp 1790762812.750424
t+5.200s  camera stamp 1790762812.814265
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+5.274s  camera stamp 1790762812.888401
t+5.333s  camera stamp 1790762812.947498
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+5.471s  camera stamp 1790762813.085618
t+5.534s  camera stamp 1790762813.147789
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+5.600s  camera stamp 1790762813.213731
t+5.667s  camera stamp 1790762813.281451
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+5.800s  camera stamp 1790762813.414098
t+5.867s  camera stamp 1790762813.481188
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+5.934s  camera stamp 1790762813.548119
t+6.000s  camera stamp 1790762813.614152
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+6.134s  camera stamp 1790762813.748146
t+6.201s  camera stamp 1790762813.815097
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+6.268s  camera stamp 1790762813.882398
t+6.335s  camera stamp 1790762813.949367
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+6.466s  camera stamp 1790762814.080531
t+6.533s  camera stamp 1790762814.147274
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+6.599s  camera stamp 1790762814.213660
t+6.666s  camera stamp 1790762814.280229
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+6.733s  camera stamp 1790762814.347272
t+6.867s  camera stamp 1790762814.481136
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+6.935s  camera stamp 1790762814.549197
t+7.000s  camera stamp 1790762814.614354
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+7.066s  camera stamp 1790762814.680392
t+7.206s  camera stamp 1790762814.819887
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+7.269s  camera stamp 1790762814.882979
t+7.334s  camera stamp 1790762814.948244
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+7.400s  camera stamp 1790762815.014382
t+7.533s  camera stamp 1790762815.147516
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+7.601s  camera stamp 1790762815.214710
t+7.667s  camera stamp 1790762815.281016
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+7.802s  camera stamp 1790762815.416528
t+7.866s  camera stamp 1790762815.480413
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+7.933s  camera stamp 1790762815.547093
t+8.000s  camera stamp 1790762815.613930
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+8.133s  camera stamp 1790762815.747441
t+8.200s  camera stamp 1790762815.813763
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+8.270s  camera stamp 1790762815.883816
t+8.333s  camera stamp 1790762815.947067
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+8.466s  camera stamp 1790762816.080511
t+8.537s  camera stamp 1790762816.150780
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+8.601s  camera stamp 1790762816.215384
t+8.667s  camera stamp 1790762816.281293
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+8.800s  camera stamp 1790762816.414395
t+8.867s  camera stamp 1790762816.480699
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+8.936s  camera stamp 1790762816.549903
t+9.000s  camera stamp 1790762816.614261
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+9.134s  camera stamp 1790762816.748431
t+9.201s  camera stamp 1790762816.814695
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+9.277s  camera stamp 1790762816.891201
t+9.343s  camera stamp 1790762816.957040
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+9.469s  camera stamp 1790762817.083066
t+9.537s  camera stamp 1790762817.151617
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+9.600s  camera stamp 1790762817.213964
t+9.667s  camera stamp 1790762817.281127
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+9.800s  camera stamp 1790762817.414577
t+9.866s  camera stamp 1790762817.480212
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+9.933s  camera stamp 1790762817.547198
t+10.001s  camera stamp 1790762817.614840
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+10.137s  camera stamp 1790762817.751001
t+10.200s  camera stamp 1790762817.813882
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+10.278s  camera stamp 1790762817.892050
t+10.338s  camera stamp 1790762817.952634
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+10.467s  camera stamp 1790762818.080786
t+10.533s  camera stamp 1790762818.146972
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+10.601s  camera stamp 1790762818.215654
t+10.668s  camera stamp 1790762818.282115
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+10.808s  camera stamp 1790762818.422529
t+10.868s  camera stamp 1790762818.481871
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+10.940s  camera stamp 1790762818.554340
t+11.066s  camera stamp 1790762818.680384
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+11.135s  camera stamp 1790762818.748794
t+11.201s  camera stamp 1790762818.814725
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+11.273s  camera stamp 1790762818.886735
t+11.400s  camera stamp 1790762819.013706
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+11.473s  camera stamp 1790762819.086679
t+11.535s  camera stamp 1790762819.149670
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+11.599s  camera stamp 1790762819.213614
t+11.734s  camera stamp 1790762819.348014
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+11.810s  camera stamp 1790762819.423881
t+11.867s  camera stamp 1790762819.480875
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+12.000s  camera stamp 1790762819.614277
t+12.067s  camera stamp 1790762819.681522
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+12.134s  camera stamp 1790762819.747876
t+12.267s  camera stamp 1790762819.881308
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+12.333s  camera stamp 1790762819.947465
t+12.407s  camera stamp 1790762820.020774
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+12.536s  camera stamp 1790762820.150598
t+12.600s  camera stamp 1790762820.214432
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+12.738s  camera stamp 1790762820.352397
t+12.802s  camera stamp 1790762820.415989
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+12.866s  camera stamp 1790762820.480282
t+13.004s  camera stamp 1790762820.618317
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+13.067s  camera stamp 1790762820.681088
t+13.133s  camera stamp 1790762820.747620
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+13.205s  camera stamp 1790762820.819409
t+13.334s  camera stamp 1790762820.947849
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+13.400s  camera stamp 1790762821.014637
t+13.467s  camera stamp 1790762821.081447
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+13.600s  camera stamp 1790762821.214563
t+13.667s  camera stamp 1790762821.280690
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+13.733s  camera stamp 1790762821.347184
t+13.866s  camera stamp 1790762821.480169
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+13.933s  camera stamp 1790762821.547406
t+14.003s  camera stamp 1790762821.617261
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+14.133s  camera stamp 1790762821.747289
t+14.200s  camera stamp 1790762821.814629
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+14.267s  camera stamp 1790762821.881042
t+14.400s  camera stamp 1790762822.014493
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+14.471s  camera stamp 1790762822.085605
t+14.533s  camera stamp 1790762822.147363
STARTUP_STRAIGHT   speed=12 steer=0  startup_straight_distance
t+14.668s  camera stamp 1790762822.281689
LANE   speed=16 steer=-2  tracking_lane
t+14.734s  camera stamp 1790762822.348018
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+14.800s  camera stamp 1790762822.414001
t+14.933s  camera stamp 1790762822.546976
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+15.005s  camera stamp 1790762822.619653
LANE   speed=16 steer=-2  tracking_lane
t+15.066s  camera stamp 1790762822.680133
t+15.200s  camera stamp 1790762822.814424
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+15.271s  camera stamp 1790762822.885484
t+15.339s  camera stamp 1790762822.953089
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+15.467s  camera stamp 1790762823.080695
t+15.533s  camera stamp 1790762823.147552
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+15.600s  camera stamp 1790762823.213870
t+15.734s  camera stamp 1790762823.348158
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+15.800s  camera stamp 1790762823.414087
LANE   speed=16 steer=-2  tracking_lane
t+15.867s  camera stamp 1790762823.480717
t+15.999s  camera stamp 1790762823.613579
LANE   speed=16 steer=0  tracking_lane
t+16.067s  camera stamp 1790762823.681638
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+16.142s  camera stamp 1790762823.755830
LANE   speed=16 steer=-6  tracking_lane
t+16.268s  camera stamp 1790762823.881805
LANE   speed=16 steer=-9  tracking_lane
t+16.338s  camera stamp 1790762823.952391
t+16.400s  camera stamp 1790762824.014005
LANE   speed=16 steer=-2  tracking_lane
t+16.470s  camera stamp 1790762824.084562
t+16.603s  camera stamp 1790762824.216927
LANE   speed=16 steer=-11  tracking_lane
t+16.667s  camera stamp 1790762824.281335
t+16.736s  camera stamp 1790762824.350470
LANE   speed=16 steer=-11  tracking_lane
t+16.866s  camera stamp 1790762824.480288
t+17.001s  camera stamp 1790762824.615098
LANE   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_lane
t+17.067s  camera stamp 1790762824.681021
LANE   speed=16 steer=-8  tracking_lane
t+17.200s  camera stamp 1790762824.814288
LANE   speed=16 steer=1  tracking_lane
t+17.334s  camera stamp 1790762824.947696
t+17.405s  camera stamp 1790762825.018705
LANE   speed=16 steer=1  tracking_lane
t+17.536s  camera stamp 1790762825.150256
t+17.668s  camera stamp 1790762825.281780
LANE   speed=16 steer=2  tracking_lane
t+17.800s  camera stamp 1790762825.413708
LANE   speed=16 steer=-7  tracking_lane
t+17.933s  camera stamp 1790762825.546905
LANE   speed=16 steer=-11  tracking_lane
t+17.999s  camera stamp 1790762825.613471
t+18.133s  camera stamp 1790762825.747030
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+18.268s  camera stamp 1790762825.881768
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+18.401s  camera stamp 1790762826.014835
LANE   speed=16 steer=-20  tracking_lane
t+18.534s  camera stamp 1790762826.147963
t+18.603s  camera stamp 1790762826.216925
LANE   speed=16 steer=-20  tracking_lane
t+18.737s  camera stamp 1790762826.350866
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+18.867s  camera stamp 1790762826.480687
t+18.939s  camera stamp 1790762826.552698
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+19.066s  camera stamp 1790762826.680038
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+19.201s  camera stamp 1790762826.814896
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+19.342s  camera stamp 1790762826.955681
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+19.399s  camera stamp 1790762827.013407
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+19.533s  camera stamp 1790762827.147053
LANE   speed=16 steer=-11  tracking_lane
t+19.666s  camera stamp 1790762827.280497
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+19.801s  camera stamp 1790762827.415404
LANE   speed=16 steer=2  tracking_lane
t+19.867s  camera stamp 1790762827.481033
LANE   speed=16 steer=1  tracking_lane
t+19.934s  camera stamp 1790762827.548483
t+20.000s  camera stamp 1790762827.614360
LANE   speed=16 steer=5  tracking_lane
t+20.133s  camera stamp 1790762827.747562
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+20.199s  camera stamp 1790762827.813559
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+20.268s  camera stamp 1790762827.882278
t+20.334s  camera stamp 1790762827.948046
LANE   speed=16 steer=7  tracking_lane
t+20.467s  camera stamp 1790762828.081289
t+20.602s  camera stamp 1790762828.216594
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+20.667s  camera stamp 1790762828.280866
LANE   speed=16 steer=10  tracking_lane
t+20.800s  camera stamp 1790762828.414329
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+20.935s  camera stamp 1790762828.549426
t+21.000s  camera stamp 1790762828.613931
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+21.133s  camera stamp 1790762828.747637
t+21.267s  camera stamp 1790762828.881137
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+21.333s  camera stamp 1790762828.947089
t+21.466s  camera stamp 1790762829.080607
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+21.600s  camera stamp 1790762829.214472
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+21.667s  camera stamp 1790762829.281453
t+21.800s  camera stamp 1790762829.414404
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+21.933s  camera stamp 1790762829.547367
t+22.067s  camera stamp 1790762829.680741
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+22.133s  camera stamp 1790762829.746832
LANE   speed=16 steer=6  tracking_lane
t+22.266s  camera stamp 1790762829.880419
t+22.401s  camera stamp 1790762830.015299
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+22.533s  camera stamp 1790762830.147183
LANE   speed=16 steer=5  tracking_lane
t+22.601s  camera stamp 1790762830.214940
LANE   speed=16 steer=4  tracking_lane
t+22.735s  camera stamp 1790762830.349675
LANE   speed=16 steer=3  tracking_lane
t+22.867s  camera stamp 1790762830.481675
LANE   speed=16 steer=4  tracking_lane
t+22.933s  camera stamp 1790762830.546930
t+23.066s  camera stamp 1790762830.680230
LANE   speed=16 steer=4  tracking_lane
t+23.200s  camera stamp 1790762830.814664
LANE   speed=16 steer=3  tracking_lane
t+23.266s  camera stamp 1790762830.880256
t+23.405s  camera stamp 1790762831.019656
LANE   speed=16 steer=2  tracking_lane
t+23.472s  camera stamp 1790762831.085840
t+23.601s  camera stamp 1790762831.215332
LANE   speed=16 steer=1  tracking_lane
t+23.735s  camera stamp 1790762831.349312
LANE   speed=16 steer=0  tracking_lane
t+23.803s  camera stamp 1790762831.417248
t+23.933s  camera stamp 1790762831.547643
LANE   speed=16 steer=0  tracking_lane
t+24.068s  camera stamp 1790762831.681717
LANE   speed=16 steer=-2  tracking_lane
t+24.199s  camera stamp 1790762831.813617
LANE   speed=16 steer=-3  tracking_lane
t+24.334s  camera stamp 1790762831.947960
LANE   speed=16 steer=-5  tracking_lane
t+24.401s  camera stamp 1790762832.015446
t+24.533s  camera stamp 1790762832.147038
LANE   speed=16 steer=-6  tracking_lane
t+24.599s  camera stamp 1790762832.213465
t+24.733s  camera stamp 1790762832.347483
LANE   speed=16 steer=-8  tracking_lane
t+24.870s  camera stamp 1790762832.484094
LANE   speed=16 steer=-9  tracking_lane
t+25.003s  camera stamp 1790762832.617295
t+25.133s  camera stamp 1790762832.747269
LANE   speed=16 steer=-13  tracking_lane
t+25.200s  camera stamp 1790762832.814144
t+25.336s  camera stamp 1790762832.950174
LANE   speed=16 steer=-11  tracking_lane
t+25.474s  camera stamp 1790762833.088545
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+25.601s  camera stamp 1790762833.215178
t+25.737s  camera stamp 1790762833.351292
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+25.868s  camera stamp 1790762833.481960
LANE   speed=16 steer=-15  tracking_lane
t+25.940s  camera stamp 1790762833.554449
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+26.067s  camera stamp 1790762833.681661
t+26.200s  camera stamp 1790762833.814422
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+26.333s  camera stamp 1790762833.947544
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+26.399s  camera stamp 1790762834.013519
t+26.473s  camera stamp 1790762834.087544
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+26.601s  camera stamp 1790762834.214863
t+26.666s  camera stamp 1790762834.280256
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+26.801s  camera stamp 1790762834.414870
LANE   speed=0 steer=-21  lane_unreliable
t+26.934s  camera stamp 1790762834.547781
t+27.000s  camera stamp 1790762834.613796
LANE   speed=0 steer=-21  lane_unreliable
t+27.133s  camera stamp 1790762834.747324
LANE   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_lane
t+27.200s  camera stamp 1790762834.814209
LANE   speed=16 steer=-13  tracking_lane
t+27.401s  camera stamp 1790762835.015122
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+27.536s  camera stamp 1790762835.150166
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+27.600s  camera stamp 1790762835.214348
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+27.804s  camera stamp 1790762835.418005
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+27.933s  camera stamp 1790762835.547388
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+28.067s  camera stamp 1790762835.680764
t+28.135s  camera stamp 1790762835.748808
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+28.337s  camera stamp 1790762835.951595
LANE   speed=16 steer=-13  tracking_lane
t+28.466s  camera stamp 1790762836.080328
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+28.599s  camera stamp 1790762836.213506
t+28.733s  camera stamp 1790762836.346935
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+28.866s  camera stamp 1790762836.480606
t+28.999s  camera stamp 1790762836.613566
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+29.133s  camera stamp 1790762836.746786
t+29.273s  camera stamp 1790762836.887152
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+29.400s  camera stamp 1790762837.014206
t+29.533s  camera stamp 1790762837.146726
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+29.667s  camera stamp 1790762837.281455
t+29.801s  camera stamp 1790762837.415289
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+29.937s  camera stamp 1790762837.551415
t+30.009s  camera stamp 1790762837.622806
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+30.200s  camera stamp 1790762837.813991
t+30.333s  camera stamp 1790762837.947496
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+30.468s  camera stamp 1790762838.081721
LANE   speed=0 steer=-22  lane_unreliable
t+30.534s  camera stamp 1790762838.148005
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+30.668s  camera stamp 1790762838.281901
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+30.741s  camera stamp 1790762838.354723
t+30.867s  camera stamp 1790762838.481238
LANE   speed=16 steer=-6  tracking_lane
t+31.000s  camera stamp 1790762838.613688
GAP   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_gap
t+31.066s  camera stamp 1790762838.680107
t+31.208s  camera stamp 1790762838.822109
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+31.400s  camera stamp 1790762839.013844
t+31.537s  camera stamp 1790762839.151477
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+31.600s  camera stamp 1790762839.214296
t+31.740s  camera stamp 1790762839.354467
LANE   speed=16 steer=-15  tracking_lane
t+31.867s  camera stamp 1790762839.481316
LANE   speed=16 steer=-13  tracking_lane
t+32.012s  camera stamp 1790762839.626316
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+32.070s  camera stamp 1790762839.683882
t+32.200s  camera stamp 1790762839.814054
LANE   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_lane
t+32.334s  camera stamp 1790762839.947966
LANE   speed=16 steer=-15  tracking_lane
t+32.403s  camera stamp 1790762840.017050
LANE   speed=16 steer=-13  tracking_lane
t+32.534s  camera stamp 1790762840.148233
GAP   speed=16 steer=-13  tracking_gap
t+32.601s  camera stamp 1790762840.215441
LANE   speed=16 steer=-4  tracking_lane
t+32.666s  camera stamp 1790762840.280201
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+32.809s  camera stamp 1790762840.423057
LANE   speed=16 steer=-4  tracking_lane
t+32.933s  camera stamp 1790762840.546867
LANE   speed=16 steer=-7  tracking_lane
t+33.000s  camera stamp 1790762840.614050
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+33.137s  camera stamp 1790762840.750974
LANE   speed=16 steer=2  tracking_lane
t+33.272s  camera stamp 1790762840.885949
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+33.403s  camera stamp 1790762841.017601
t+33.470s  camera stamp 1790762841.084583
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+33.600s  camera stamp 1790762841.213903
LANE   speed=16 steer=-13  tracking_lane
t+33.734s  camera stamp 1790762841.347789
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+33.800s  camera stamp 1790762841.413772
t+33.933s  camera stamp 1790762841.547355
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+34.067s  camera stamp 1790762841.681439
t+34.134s  camera stamp 1790762841.747693
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+34.266s  camera stamp 1790762841.880425
t+34.403s  camera stamp 1790762842.017006
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+34.474s  camera stamp 1790762842.088108
t+34.599s  camera stamp 1790762842.213664
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+34.739s  camera stamp 1790762842.353618
t+34.808s  camera stamp 1790762842.422203
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+34.933s  camera stamp 1790762842.547211
t+35.066s  camera stamp 1790762842.680528
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+35.135s  camera stamp 1790762842.749247
t+35.267s  camera stamp 1790762842.881134
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+35.333s  camera stamp 1790762842.947514
t+35.466s  camera stamp 1790762843.080422
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+35.601s  camera stamp 1790762843.215005
t+35.671s  camera stamp 1790762843.285083
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+35.803s  camera stamp 1790762843.416800
t+35.867s  camera stamp 1790762843.480723
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+35.999s  camera stamp 1790762843.613631
t+36.134s  camera stamp 1790762843.748603
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+36.271s  camera stamp 1790762843.885223
t+36.333s  camera stamp 1790762843.947204
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+36.472s  camera stamp 1790762844.086208
t+36.535s  camera stamp 1790762844.148862
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+36.666s  camera stamp 1790762844.280532
LANE   speed=16 steer=-20  tracking_lane
t+36.800s  camera stamp 1790762844.414607
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+36.867s  camera stamp 1790762844.481475
t+37.000s  camera stamp 1790762844.614423
LANE   speed=16 steer=-20  tracking_lane
t+37.133s  camera stamp 1790762844.747432
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+37.202s  camera stamp 1790762844.816256
t+37.333s  camera stamp 1790762844.946832
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+37.404s  camera stamp 1790762845.018598
LANE   speed=16 steer=-15  tracking_lane
t+37.533s  camera stamp 1790762845.147368
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+37.600s  camera stamp 1790762845.214424
t+37.670s  camera stamp 1790762845.284375
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+37.801s  camera stamp 1790762845.415221
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+37.867s  camera stamp 1790762845.480681
t+37.939s  camera stamp 1790762845.553580
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+38.068s  camera stamp 1790762845.682241
LANE   speed=16 steer=-10  tracking_lane
t+38.137s  camera stamp 1790762845.751224
t+38.272s  camera stamp 1790762845.886539
LANE   speed=16 steer=-10  tracking_lane
t+38.337s  camera stamp 1790762845.951336
t+38.466s  camera stamp 1790762846.080423
LANE   speed=16 steer=-8  tracking_lane
t+38.534s  camera stamp 1790762846.148190
LANE   speed=16 steer=-6  tracking_lane
t+38.601s  camera stamp 1790762846.214975
t+38.733s  camera stamp 1790762846.347222
LANE   speed=16 steer=-6  tracking_lane
t+38.801s  camera stamp 1790762846.415125
t+38.936s  camera stamp 1790762846.549731
LANE   speed=16 steer=-8  tracking_lane
t+39.005s  camera stamp 1790762846.619092
t+39.067s  camera stamp 1790762846.681338
LANE   speed=16 steer=-6  tracking_lane
t+39.201s  camera stamp 1790762846.815612
LANE   speed=16 steer=-5  tracking_lane
t+39.268s  camera stamp 1790762846.881839
t+39.401s  camera stamp 1790762847.015117
LANE   speed=16 steer=-2  tracking_lane
t+39.467s  camera stamp 1790762847.080865
LANE   speed=16 steer=-3  tracking_lane
t+39.533s  camera stamp 1790762847.147508
t+39.667s  camera stamp 1790762847.280767
LANE   speed=16 steer=-3  tracking_lane
t+39.733s  camera stamp 1790762847.347505
LANE   speed=16 steer=-2  tracking_lane
t+39.867s  camera stamp 1790762847.481286
LANE   speed=16 steer=1  tracking_lane
t+39.934s  camera stamp 1790762847.547814
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+40.004s  camera stamp 1790762847.617715
t+40.135s  camera stamp 1790762847.748709
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=0 steer=22  bypass_settle_left
t+40.206s  camera stamp 1790762847.819680
t+40.333s  camera stamp 1790762847.947158
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=0 steer=22  bypass_settle_left
t+40.404s  camera stamp 1790762848.018024
t+40.533s  camera stamp 1790762848.147634
TIMED_BYPASS SETTLE_LEFT  speed=0 steer=22  bypass_settle_left
t+40.601s  camera stamp 1790762848.215410
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+40.667s  camera stamp 1790762848.281634
t+40.802s  camera stamp 1790762848.416618
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+40.867s  camera stamp 1790762848.480806
t+40.934s  camera stamp 1790762848.548398
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+41.067s  camera stamp 1790762848.681194
t+41.133s  camera stamp 1790762848.747483
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+41.268s  camera stamp 1790762848.882438
t+41.333s  camera stamp 1790762848.947325
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+41.399s  camera stamp 1790762849.013638
t+41.533s  camera stamp 1790762849.147357
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+41.600s  camera stamp 1790762849.214078
t+41.675s  camera stamp 1790762849.289017
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+41.802s  camera stamp 1790762849.416072
t+41.870s  camera stamp 1790762849.484127
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+42.001s  camera stamp 1790762849.614771
t+42.067s  camera stamp 1790762849.681190
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+42.133s  camera stamp 1790762849.747501
t+42.278s  camera stamp 1790762849.892552
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+42.333s  camera stamp 1790762849.947131
t+42.473s  camera stamp 1790762850.087101
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_left_2s
t+42.533s  camera stamp 1790762850.147403
t+42.666s  camera stamp 1790762850.280599
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_extend_left_for_clearance
t+42.803s  camera stamp 1790762850.417128
t+42.866s  camera stamp 1790762850.480173
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_extend_left_for_clearance
t+43.000s  camera stamp 1790762850.614274
t+43.133s  camera stamp 1790762850.747108
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=22  bypass_extend_left_for_clearance
t+43.201s  camera stamp 1790762850.815537
t+43.334s  camera stamp 1790762850.947757
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+43.481s  camera stamp 1790762851.094769
t+43.601s  camera stamp 1790762851.214819
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+43.734s  camera stamp 1790762851.347772
t+43.802s  camera stamp 1790762851.416047
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+43.934s  camera stamp 1790762851.548050
t+44.001s  camera stamp 1790762851.615641
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+44.133s  camera stamp 1790762851.747446
t+44.201s  camera stamp 1790762851.814897
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+44.334s  camera stamp 1790762851.948466
t+44.402s  camera stamp 1790762852.015909
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+44.533s  camera stamp 1790762852.147541
t+44.602s  camera stamp 1790762852.216665
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+44.733s  camera stamp 1790762852.347500
t+44.867s  camera stamp 1790762852.481336
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+45.000s  camera stamp 1790762852.614057
t+45.067s  camera stamp 1790762852.681170
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+45.201s  camera stamp 1790762852.814949
t+45.333s  camera stamp 1790762852.947002
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+45.400s  camera stamp 1790762853.014649
t+45.533s  camera stamp 1790762853.146810
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+45.601s  camera stamp 1790762853.214857
t+45.733s  camera stamp 1790762853.347292
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+45.801s  camera stamp 1790762853.415187
t+45.934s  camera stamp 1790762853.548241
TIMED_BYPASS   speed=24 steer=-22  bypass_right_6s
t+46.068s  camera stamp 1790762853.682156
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  bypass_heading_lane_handoff
t+46.145s  camera stamp 1790762853.759408
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+46.281s  camera stamp 1790762853.894832
t+46.400s  camera stamp 1790762854.014030
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+46.467s  camera stamp 1790762854.081535
t+46.599s  camera stamp 1790762854.213622
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+46.733s  camera stamp 1790762854.347369
t+46.809s  camera stamp 1790762854.423027
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+46.933s  camera stamp 1790762854.547524
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+47.068s  camera stamp 1790762854.681822
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+47.133s  camera stamp 1790762854.747350
t+47.268s  camera stamp 1790762854.882546
LANE   speed=16 steer=-15  tracking_lane
t+47.400s  camera stamp 1790762855.014444
t+47.468s  camera stamp 1790762855.082618
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+47.537s  camera stamp 1790762855.151222
t+47.667s  camera stamp 1790762855.281482
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+47.800s  camera stamp 1790762855.414664
t+47.867s  camera stamp 1790762855.480709
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+48.003s  camera stamp 1790762855.617066
LANE   speed=16 steer=-20  tracking_lane
t+48.133s  camera stamp 1790762855.747129
t+48.205s  camera stamp 1790762855.819506
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+48.336s  camera stamp 1790762855.950403
t+48.401s  camera stamp 1790762856.014947
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+48.534s  camera stamp 1790762856.147738
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+48.667s  camera stamp 1790762856.281022
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+48.804s  camera stamp 1790762856.417715
t+48.933s  camera stamp 1790762856.547238
LANE   speed=16 steer=-20  tracking_lane
t+48.999s  camera stamp 1790762856.613606
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+49.133s  camera stamp 1790762856.747358
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+49.278s  camera stamp 1790762856.891888
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+49.400s  camera stamp 1790762857.014235
LANE   speed=16 steer=-20  tracking_lane
t+49.476s  camera stamp 1790762857.089915
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+49.602s  camera stamp 1790762857.216168
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+49.733s  camera stamp 1790762857.347199
LANE   speed=16 steer=-9  tracking_lane
t+49.870s  camera stamp 1790762857.483972
LANE   speed=16 steer=-7  tracking_lane
t+49.933s  camera stamp 1790762857.547294
LANE   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_lane
t+50.003s  camera stamp 1790762857.617637
t+50.067s  camera stamp 1790762857.681040
LANE   speed=16 steer=-7  tracking_lane
t+50.141s  camera stamp 1790762857.755010
t+50.267s  camera stamp 1790762857.881418
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+50.333s  camera stamp 1790762857.947124
t+50.401s  camera stamp 1790762858.015601
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+50.467s  camera stamp 1790762858.080972
LANE   speed=16 steer=6  tracking_lane
t+50.601s  camera stamp 1790762858.215333
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+50.668s  camera stamp 1790762858.281921
t+50.737s  camera stamp 1790762858.351526
LANE   speed=16 steer=3  tracking_lane
t+50.800s  camera stamp 1790762858.414154
t+50.871s  camera stamp 1790762858.485043
LANE   speed=16 steer=-5  tracking_lane
t+51.002s  camera stamp 1790762858.615987
LANE   speed=16 steer=-6  tracking_lane
t+51.066s  camera stamp 1790762858.680536
LANE   speed=16 steer=-1  tracking_lane
t+51.133s  camera stamp 1790762858.747144
LANE   speed=16 steer=-10  tracking_lane
t+51.201s  camera stamp 1790762858.815663
t+51.269s  camera stamp 1790762858.883267
LANE   speed=16 steer=-10  tracking_lane
t+51.402s  camera stamp 1790762859.015738
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+51.467s  camera stamp 1790762859.080841
t+51.535s  camera stamp 1790762859.148874
LANE   speed=16 steer=-18  tracking_lane
t+51.667s  camera stamp 1790762859.280780
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+51.735s  camera stamp 1790762859.349669
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+51.802s  camera stamp 1790762859.415838
t+51.933s  camera stamp 1790762859.547623
LANE   speed=16 steer=-15  tracking_lane
t+52.002s  camera stamp 1790762859.615829
t+52.067s  camera stamp 1790762859.680965
LANE   speed=16 steer=-15  tracking_lane
t+52.134s  camera stamp 1790762859.747874
t+52.201s  camera stamp 1790762859.814931
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+52.336s  camera stamp 1790762859.949978
t+52.400s  camera stamp 1790762860.014159
LANE   speed=16 steer=-14  tracking_lane
t+52.473s  camera stamp 1790762860.087488
LANE   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_lane
t+52.539s  camera stamp 1790762860.153090
t+52.602s  camera stamp 1790762860.215944
LANE   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_lane
t+52.667s  camera stamp 1790762860.280863
t+52.743s  camera stamp 1790762860.357156
GAP   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_gap
t+52.801s  camera stamp 1790762860.415356
t+52.867s  camera stamp 1790762860.480795
GAP   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_gap
t+52.937s  camera stamp 1790762860.551294
t+53.001s  camera stamp 1790762860.614847
GAP   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_gap
t+53.133s  camera stamp 1790762860.747335
t+53.204s  camera stamp 1790762860.818009
GAP   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_gap
t+53.267s  camera stamp 1790762860.881068
t+53.333s  camera stamp 1790762860.947163
GAP   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_gap
t+53.467s  camera stamp 1790762861.081620
t+53.537s  camera stamp 1790762861.150795
GAP   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_gap
t+53.600s  camera stamp 1790762861.214544
t+53.667s  camera stamp 1790762861.280693
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+53.807s  camera stamp 1790762861.420898
t+53.866s  camera stamp 1790762861.480423
LANE   speed=16 steer=-21  tracking_lane
t+53.935s  camera stamp 1790762861.549541
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+54.066s  camera stamp 1790762861.680671
t+54.133s  camera stamp 1790762861.747562
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+54.202s  camera stamp 1790762861.815729
t+54.279s  camera stamp 1790762861.892754
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+54.340s  camera stamp 1790762861.953725
t+54.475s  camera stamp 1790762862.089172
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+54.534s  camera stamp 1790762862.147762
t+54.600s  camera stamp 1790762862.214134
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+54.668s  camera stamp 1790762862.282294
t+54.800s  camera stamp 1790762862.414467
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+54.867s  camera stamp 1790762862.480765
t+54.933s  camera stamp 1790762862.547464
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+55.001s  camera stamp 1790762862.614806
t+55.137s  camera stamp 1790762862.750938
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+55.202s  camera stamp 1790762862.815730
t+55.267s  camera stamp 1790762862.881013
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+55.335s  camera stamp 1790762862.949479
t+55.466s  camera stamp 1790762863.080369
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+55.533s  camera stamp 1790762863.147411
t+55.601s  camera stamp 1790762863.214798
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+55.667s  camera stamp 1790762863.280735
t+55.804s  camera stamp 1790762863.417960
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+55.866s  camera stamp 1790762863.480446
t+55.944s  camera stamp 1790762863.558095
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+56.006s  camera stamp 1790762863.620003
t+56.133s  camera stamp 1790762863.747070
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+56.200s  camera stamp 1790762863.814189
t+56.271s  camera stamp 1790762863.885000
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+56.333s  camera stamp 1790762863.947282
t+56.473s  camera stamp 1790762864.086882
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+56.533s  camera stamp 1790762864.147337
LANE   speed=16 steer=-17  tracking_lane
t+56.600s  camera stamp 1790762864.214214
LANE   speed=16 steer=-19  tracking_lane
t+56.667s  camera stamp 1790762864.280945
LANE   speed=16 steer=-22  tracking_lane
t+56.801s  camera stamp 1790762864.415453
LANE   speed=16 steer=-16  tracking_lane
t+56.871s  camera stamp 1790762864.485023
t+56.933s  camera stamp 1790762864.547335
GAP   speed=16 steer=-8  tracking_gap
t+57.002s  camera stamp 1790762864.616592
GAP   speed=0 steer=-8  lane_unreliable
t+57.070s  camera stamp 1790762864.683956
LANE   speed=16 steer=1  tracking_lane
t+57.200s  camera stamp 1790762864.814100
t+57.274s  camera stamp 1790762864.887748
LANE   speed=16 steer=6  tracking_lane
t+57.334s  camera stamp 1790762864.947780
t+57.404s  camera stamp 1790762865.018308
LANE   speed=16 steer=10  tracking_lane
t+57.533s  camera stamp 1790762865.147096
t+57.600s  camera stamp 1790762865.213713
LANE   speed=16 steer=1  tracking_lane
t+57.667s  camera stamp 1790762865.280709
LANE   speed=16 steer=7  tracking_lane
t+57.803s  camera stamp 1790762865.417455
LANE   speed=16 steer=-8  tracking_lane
t+57.867s  camera stamp 1790762865.480870
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+57.935s  camera stamp 1790762865.549091
t+58.066s  camera stamp 1790762865.680321
LANE   speed=16 steer=4  tracking_lane
t+58.133s  camera stamp 1790762865.747546
t+58.200s  camera stamp 1790762865.813962
LANE   speed=16 steer=12  tracking_lane
t+58.334s  camera stamp 1790762865.948455
LANE   speed=16 steer=2  tracking_lane
t+58.401s  camera stamp 1790762866.015576
LANE   speed=16 steer=10  tracking_lane
t+58.479s  camera stamp 1790762866.093635
t+58.534s  camera stamp 1790762866.148419
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+58.667s  camera stamp 1790762866.280895
LANE   speed=16 steer=9  tracking_lane
t+58.733s  camera stamp 1790762866.347532
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+58.801s  camera stamp 1790762866.415272
t+58.936s  camera stamp 1790762866.550114
LANE   speed=16 steer=7  tracking_lane
t+59.001s  camera stamp 1790762866.615453
t+59.067s  camera stamp 1790762866.680738
LANE   speed=16 steer=6  tracking_lane
t+59.204s  camera stamp 1790762866.818070
LANE   speed=16 steer=8  tracking_lane
t+59.267s  camera stamp 1790762866.881351
LANE   speed=16 steer=6  tracking_lane
t+59.335s  camera stamp 1790762866.949006
t+59.468s  camera stamp 1790762867.082540
LANE   speed=0 steer=6  lane_unreliable
t+59.537s  camera stamp 1790762867.150872
t+59.600s  camera stamp 1790762867.213692
GAP   speed=16 steer=6  tracking_gap
t+59.666s  camera stamp 1790762867.280407
t+59.733s  camera stamp 1790762867.347166
GAP   speed=16 steer=6  tracking_gap
t+59.866s  camera stamp 1790762867.480530
LANE   speed=16 steer=-3  tracking_lane
t+60.003s  camera stamp 1790762867.617065
LANE   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_lane
t+60.072s  camera stamp 1790762867.686270
LANE   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+60.201s  camera stamp 1790762867.815363
t+60.273s  camera stamp 1790762867.886988
LANE   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+60.401s  camera stamp 1790762868.015372
t+60.471s  camera stamp 1790762868.085236
LANE   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+60.603s  camera stamp 1790762868.216879
GAP   speed=16 steer=-12  tracking_gap
t+60.666s  camera stamp 1790762868.280421
t+60.800s  camera stamp 1790762868.413965
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+60.869s  camera stamp 1790762868.482827
t+61.000s  camera stamp 1790762868.613743
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+61.068s  camera stamp 1790762868.681699
t+61.133s  camera stamp 1790762868.747639
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+61.267s  camera stamp 1790762868.881333
t+61.333s  camera stamp 1790762868.947390
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+61.466s  camera stamp 1790762869.080535
t+61.533s  camera stamp 1790762869.147126
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+61.668s  camera stamp 1790762869.282567
t+61.733s  camera stamp 1790762869.347282
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+61.868s  camera stamp 1790762869.482229
t+61.934s  camera stamp 1790762869.548139
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+62.067s  camera stamp 1790762869.681135
t+62.135s  camera stamp 1790762869.749066
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+62.200s  camera stamp 1790762869.813910
t+62.333s  camera stamp 1790762869.947173
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+62.400s  camera stamp 1790762870.013749
t+62.533s  camera stamp 1790762870.146974
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+62.599s  camera stamp 1790762870.213674
t+62.733s  camera stamp 1790762870.347213
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+62.808s  camera stamp 1790762870.421995
t+62.933s  camera stamp 1790762870.547112
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+63.005s  camera stamp 1790762870.619385
t+63.133s  camera stamp 1790762870.747597
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+63.203s  camera stamp 1790762870.817291
t+63.333s  camera stamp 1790762870.947450
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+63.401s  camera stamp 1790762871.014881
t+63.536s  camera stamp 1790762871.150593
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+63.600s  camera stamp 1790762871.213700
t+63.735s  camera stamp 1790762871.349128
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+63.803s  camera stamp 1790762871.417528
t+63.933s  camera stamp 1790762871.547397
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+64.002s  camera stamp 1790762871.616106
t+64.068s  camera stamp 1790762871.682309
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+64.202s  camera stamp 1790762871.816187
t+64.334s  camera stamp 1790762871.947998
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+64.400s  camera stamp 1790762872.014297
t+64.470s  camera stamp 1790762872.084656
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+64.601s  camera stamp 1790762872.215068
t+64.668s  camera stamp 1790762872.282272
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+65.006s  camera stamp 1790762872.620135
t+65.077s  camera stamp 1790762872.690761
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+65.200s  camera stamp 1790762872.813887
t+65.343s  camera stamp 1790762872.956884
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+65.400s  camera stamp 1790762873.013943
t+65.537s  camera stamp 1790762873.151073
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+65.666s  camera stamp 1790762873.280559
t+65.735s  camera stamp 1790762873.349103
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+65.868s  camera stamp 1790762873.481987
t+65.935s  camera stamp 1790762873.548792
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+66.068s  camera stamp 1790762873.681807
t+66.136s  camera stamp 1790762873.750620
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+66.270s  camera stamp 1790762873.883759
t+66.333s  camera stamp 1790762873.947045
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+66.400s  camera stamp 1790762874.014603
t+66.537s  camera stamp 1790762874.151485
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+66.606s  camera stamp 1790762874.220178
t+66.741s  camera stamp 1790762874.354680
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+66.801s  camera stamp 1790762874.414702
t+66.936s  camera stamp 1790762874.549806
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+67.006s  camera stamp 1790762874.619796
t+67.137s  camera stamp 1790762874.750872
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+67.201s  camera stamp 1790762874.815545
t+67.334s  camera stamp 1790762874.948626
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+67.401s  camera stamp 1790762875.014769
t+67.535s  camera stamp 1790762875.149345
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+67.608s  camera stamp 1790762875.222474
t+67.669s  camera stamp 1790762875.283185
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+67.812s  camera stamp 1790762875.425779
t+67.934s  camera stamp 1790762875.547703
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+68.000s  camera stamp 1790762875.614256
t+68.069s  camera stamp 1790762875.683664
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+68.202s  camera stamp 1790762875.816504
t+68.271s  camera stamp 1790762875.885360
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+68.403s  camera stamp 1790762876.017576
t+68.479s  camera stamp 1790762876.092818
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+68.601s  camera stamp 1790762876.214987
t+68.667s  camera stamp 1790762876.280755
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+68.801s  camera stamp 1790762876.414750
t+68.867s  camera stamp 1790762876.480838
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+68.934s  camera stamp 1790762876.548541
t+69.069s  camera stamp 1790762876.682856
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+69.134s  camera stamp 1790762876.747936
t+69.268s  camera stamp 1790762876.882227
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+69.336s  camera stamp 1790762876.950398
t+69.471s  camera stamp 1790762877.085161
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+69.539s  camera stamp 1790762877.152767
t+69.667s  camera stamp 1790762877.280754
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+69.733s  camera stamp 1790762877.347596
t+69.867s  camera stamp 1790762877.480889
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+69.940s  camera stamp 1790762877.553997
t+70.068s  camera stamp 1790762877.682108
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+70.134s  camera stamp 1790762877.748106
t+70.267s  camera stamp 1790762877.880907
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+70.333s  camera stamp 1790762877.947438
t+70.470s  camera stamp 1790762878.084454
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+70.534s  camera stamp 1790762878.147806
t+70.600s  camera stamp 1790762878.214339
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+70.734s  camera stamp 1790762878.347930
t+70.867s  camera stamp 1790762878.480859
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+70.935s  camera stamp 1790762878.548682
t+71.000s  camera stamp 1790762878.613842
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+71.136s  camera stamp 1790762878.750664
t+71.207s  camera stamp 1790762878.820719
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+71.333s  camera stamp 1790762878.947624
t+71.401s  camera stamp 1790762879.015060
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+71.543s  camera stamp 1790762879.157225
t+71.601s  camera stamp 1790762879.214965
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+71.736s  camera stamp 1790762879.350321
t+71.806s  camera stamp 1790762879.419963
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+71.933s  camera stamp 1790762879.547064
t+72.006s  camera stamp 1790762879.620062
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+72.067s  camera stamp 1790762879.681090
t+72.201s  camera stamp 1790762879.815119
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+72.333s  camera stamp 1790762879.947488
t+72.401s  camera stamp 1790762880.015259
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+72.475s  camera stamp 1790762880.089204
t+72.601s  camera stamp 1790762880.214964
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+72.733s  camera stamp 1790762880.347010
t+72.804s  camera stamp 1790762880.418659
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+72.935s  camera stamp 1790762880.549351
t+73.008s  camera stamp 1790762880.621933
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+73.133s  camera stamp 1790762880.747550
t+73.200s  camera stamp 1790762880.814164
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+73.334s  camera stamp 1790762880.947914
t+73.402s  camera stamp 1790762881.015880
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+73.536s  camera stamp 1790762881.149697
t+73.601s  camera stamp 1790762881.215482
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+73.734s  camera stamp 1790762881.347881
t+73.810s  camera stamp 1790762881.424524
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+73.933s  camera stamp 1790762881.547426
t+74.005s  camera stamp 1790762881.619060
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+74.133s  camera stamp 1790762881.747420
t+74.206s  camera stamp 1790762881.820314
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+74.333s  camera stamp 1790762881.947646
t+74.404s  camera stamp 1790762882.017982
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+74.537s  camera stamp 1790762882.151453
t+74.600s  camera stamp 1790762882.214234
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+74.734s  camera stamp 1790762882.347701
t+74.805s  camera stamp 1790762882.419616
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+74.936s  camera stamp 1790762882.549997
t+75.000s  camera stamp 1790762882.614517
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+75.072s  camera stamp 1790762882.685739
t+75.201s  camera stamp 1790762882.815346
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+75.334s  camera stamp 1790762882.947747
t+75.400s  camera stamp 1790762883.014540
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+75.533s  camera stamp 1790762883.147259
t+75.600s  camera stamp 1790762883.214271
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+75.668s  camera stamp 1790762883.282005
t+75.800s  camera stamp 1790762883.414063
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+75.933s  camera stamp 1790762883.547400
t+76.003s  camera stamp 1790762883.616711
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+76.067s  camera stamp 1790762883.681312
t+76.200s  camera stamp 1790762883.813950
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+76.333s  camera stamp 1790762883.947195
t+76.401s  camera stamp 1790762884.014842
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+76.467s  camera stamp 1790762884.080921
t+76.601s  camera stamp 1790762884.215012
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+76.733s  camera stamp 1790762884.347368
t+76.807s  camera stamp 1790762884.421414
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+76.937s  camera stamp 1790762884.551196
t+77.001s  camera stamp 1790762884.615650
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+77.136s  camera stamp 1790762884.750333
t+77.201s  camera stamp 1790762884.814757
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+77.340s  camera stamp 1790762884.953843
t+77.400s  camera stamp 1790762885.013982
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+77.539s  camera stamp 1790762885.153435
t+77.600s  camera stamp 1790762885.214033
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+77.735s  camera stamp 1790762885.349222
t+77.801s  camera stamp 1790762885.415246
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+77.934s  camera stamp 1790762885.547745
t+78.000s  camera stamp 1790762885.614347
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+78.135s  camera stamp 1790762885.749482
t+78.269s  camera stamp 1790762885.883059
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+78.334s  camera stamp 1790762885.947796
t+78.402s  camera stamp 1790762886.015715
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+78.534s  camera stamp 1790762886.147755
t+78.667s  camera stamp 1790762886.281032
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+78.736s  camera stamp 1790762886.350150
t+78.866s  camera stamp 1790762886.480532
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+78.933s  camera stamp 1790762886.547668
t+79.068s  camera stamp 1790762886.682055
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+79.201s  camera stamp 1790762886.814754
t+79.271s  camera stamp 1790762886.885567
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+79.400s  camera stamp 1790762887.014015
t+79.470s  camera stamp 1790762887.084044
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+79.600s  camera stamp 1790762887.213840
t+79.666s  camera stamp 1790762887.280647
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+79.810s  camera stamp 1790762887.424085
t+79.867s  camera stamp 1790762887.480925
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+80.000s  camera stamp 1790762887.613863
t+80.133s  camera stamp 1790762887.747265
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+80.200s  camera stamp 1790762887.814199
t+80.334s  camera stamp 1790762887.947821
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+80.402s  camera stamp 1790762888.015860
t+80.541s  camera stamp 1790762888.155109
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+80.602s  camera stamp 1790762888.215678
t+80.741s  camera stamp 1790762888.355167
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+80.868s  camera stamp 1790762888.481883
t+80.933s  camera stamp 1790762888.547403
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+81.066s  camera stamp 1790762888.680479
t+81.133s  camera stamp 1790762888.747593
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+81.268s  camera stamp 1790762888.881877
t+81.335s  camera stamp 1790762888.949267
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+81.470s  camera stamp 1790762889.084021
t+81.534s  camera stamp 1790762889.148284
GAP   speed=0 steer=-12  lane_unreliable
t+81.667s  camera stamp 1790762889.281365